A Guide to the VCU Libraries Zine collection, 1979-2017
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library
VCU Libraries Zine collection, 1979-2017
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 560
9.24 linear feet.
VCU Libraries
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donations received from multiple sources since the 1990s.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains approximately 700 zines that were acquired from multiple sources and donors since the 1990s. Self-published by individuals or produced by small groups, the zines represent a wide range of genres including political, personal, DIY, and art zines among others. Many of the zines were created in Virginia or have a connection to Virginia Commonwealth University, but there are also hundreds of zines from other locations, primarily in the United States. Zines that were offered during the annual Richmond Zine Festival since its inception in 2007, are featured prominently in the collection.
Arrangement
Zines are arranged alphabetically by title.
- 7 Layers of Recipes, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 10 Years of the Portland Zine Symposium, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 12 Inch T Square, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 12 Pack Adventure, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 13 Years of Good Luck, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 24 hour mini comic fun, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 24 Pages, 24 Games, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Twenty-eight Pages Lovingly Bound with Twine, no. 3, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Twenty-eight Pages Lovingly Bound with Twine, no. 4, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Mondo Bizarro, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ab, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Abortion Poems, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Academy Ratio, no. 3, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Add zine, no. 1 Poster Issue, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- After Thought, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Aggy Poz, no. 1, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- All New Super Hot Beaver Action, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Alone on Prom Night, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alone on Prom Night Drawings and Musings, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Amazing Science Digest, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Ameoba, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Amnesia 666, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- amoury issue, no. 1, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- An Alphabet of Alodon, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Anarchy Ad Libs, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Anarchy and Antifa, vol. 1, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Anartchism, no. 1, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Anemone Mine, no. 1-3, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Animal Poems and Animal Colors, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Ann Cendiiary, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Annus Horribilis, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Anok n' Proud, no. 4, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- another name for nothing, issue 4, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Applicant, 1998-2002; 1998-2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- the art of politics, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
- as the world burns, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Ask First!, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ASWAN's News Cut, vol. 1, no. 9, vol. 2, no. 1, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- August in Harveyville Poems and Experiences of Chantel C. Guidry, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Autopilot, no. 6, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Autumn Poem, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Baba's Accordion, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Badzine 5 issues, 2010, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bake and Destroy everyone around you, 2 issues, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- The Barber Shop News, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Barnard Zine Library Zine, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Beach is that Way, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- bee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- bee: One-year anniversary issue Devoted to sed 2-1, vol. 1, 12, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Ben Folds The National RVA!, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Best of Poet-in-the-Box, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Best of Shebytchesb, no. 1, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Better Not, no. 1, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- beyond a joke, no. 3, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Bi Lines, vol. 2, no. 9, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Bi Lines, vol. 3, no. 3, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Big Sister, no. 2, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Bitch, no. 6, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Black Liquid, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Blackbird Coyote, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Blood and Guts, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
- blood cunt, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- blurt: from the mind to the medium, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Blurry Line, The, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Book of Games, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Booty Call, 2 issues, 2006, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Borderland Dispatches, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- brainscan, no. 19, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
- brainscan, no. 22, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- brainscan, no. 24, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- brainscan, no. 25, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- brainscan, no. 25.5, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brainscan Epilogue, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Breakfast at Twilight, no. 2-3, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Breakfast at Twilight, no. 5, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Brewtopia: Peace, Equality, Booze, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Buffy, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Big Prick, no. 6, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Building a Life with Limp Wrists, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Built Beaty, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Burn Collector, no. 16, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- But a Paper Dress, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Candy Box: An Adventure in Sweets from the UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Capitol City Arts Magazine, no. 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Cat Power, no. 13, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Catharsis, no. 2, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Catharsis, no. 3, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Catharsis, no. 6, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Catharsis, no. 8, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Catherine's Hair, no. 6-7, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Catherine's Hair, no. 8-9 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Caution!, no.1, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Caution!, vol. 1 no. 3, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Caution!, vol. 1 no. 4, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Celestial Bodies and My Sex, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Chalaza, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Change the world in 7 days, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Cheaptoys, no. 5.5, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cheesecake, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Cheesecloth, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Childlike Empress, no. 0, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Childlike Empress, no. 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Childress Empress, no. 1.5, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Chord Easy, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Chump, no. 2-3, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Chump, no. 4-5, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- The CIA Makes Science Fiction Unexciting, no. 3, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- The CIA Makes Science Fiction Unexciting, no. 5, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cometbus, no. 32, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Cometbus, no. 33, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cometbus, no. 34, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cometbus, no. 35, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Cometbus, no. 36, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Cometbus, no. 39, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Cometbus, no. 40, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Cometbus, no. 41, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cometbus, no. 42, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Cometbus, no. 43, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Cometbus, no. 44, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cometbus, no. 45, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Cometbus, no. 46, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cometbus, no. 47, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cometbus, no. 48, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cometbus, no. 49, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Cometbus, no. 50, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Cometbus, no. 51, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Cometbus, no. 52, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- The Confederate Mack, Top 10 Collection, no. 1-20, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 1-3, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 4-6, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 7-9, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 10-12, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 13-15, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 16-18, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 19-21, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 22-24, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 25-27, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 28-30, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 31-33, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 34-36, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 37-39, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 40, 42, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 43, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 46-47, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 48, 50, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- The Confederate Mack, no. 51, 52, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- The Confederate Mack, 3 issues without issue numbers, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Confession to Cory, no. 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Convoluted Comin Strips, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Crazed Mazes, no. 2, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Crazy Christian Conspiracy Comics, no. 1-3, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
- The Crime of Politics in America and the Politics of Crime, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- The Crooked Rascal, no. 6, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- cruentus odium, no. 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Crushpuppy, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Crust, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cryptic Slaughter, no. 25, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cuddle Puddles and Hot Pants, no. 2-3, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Cuddle Puddles and Hot Pants, no. 4-5, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Culture Vulture, no. 1, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Cup and Saucer Chronicles, no. 1, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Current Resident, no. 1-2, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Cute Girl, no. 1, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Cute Girl, no. 2, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- D.I.Y., no. 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Damn Engine!, no. 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Dangeresque, no. 1-2, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Day Dream, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Day I Quit Punk Rock, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- DDK Issue 2: Better Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Deadramones, vol. II, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Dear America, I'm Lost, no. 2,4, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Destiny, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- The Death of Antisocial man, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- the death of a salesman, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- dimwit, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Dirt Worst, no. 1, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Dirt Worst, no. 4, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Dirty Love and Fiberglass Smiles, issues 1, 2, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Discharge, no. 3, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Discomfort, no. 1, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Discomfort: One Man's Trash is Another Man's Zine, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Dish Washer, no. 15, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Dixie Phoenix, no. 8, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Do Not Disturb, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Doctor Sputnik, no. 1-2, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- The Doctrine of Hell, no. 1, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Don't Leave Your Friends Behind, no. 2, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Don't Say Un-Oh, no.15, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Don't Tread on Me, no. 6-7, 2009, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Don't Tread on Me, no. 9, 11-12, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Don't Tread on Me, no. 34, 41.5, 42, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Don't Tread on Me, no. 44-45, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Don't Tread on Me, no. 48, 50, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dookie on a Stick, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Doris, no. 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Doris, no. 23, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Doris, no. 25, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
- The Drama, no. 1, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Dreamy vs. Sucks, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Drive for Eternity, no. 2, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Dub Riders, no. 5, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- E.Y.E.: Eat Your Eyeballs, no. 1, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Eastern Paralyzed Veterans of America, no. 1-2, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- The East Village Inky, no. 16, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- The East Village Inky, no. 22, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- The East Village Inky, no. 36, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Eat Yer Heart Out, Martha, no. 1-2, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
- The Edgy-catin' Mama, no. 3, 5, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Edward, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Empower Yr Sexy Self: A Workbook, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
- End of the !@no.%^* Road, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Energy Germs, no. 1, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Entropy, no. 4-6, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Entry Point, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Escaping Suburbia, no. 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Every Other, no. 10, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Every Other, no. 13, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Exile Magazine, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- F - Art, 4 issues, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
- The F-Bombs, no. 3, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- F. T. W., no. 5, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Factsheet 5, no. 23, 53, 1987, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Faerie, no.18, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Faulty Television, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Femme a Barbee, no. 1-2, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
- The Ferry-Traders Guide to Government, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- The Fest Oh 8 The Zine, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Fever, no. 1-2, 1996, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- A Few More Things that Richmond and VCU Think of You and Your Kind, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Fight Back! yr guide to feminist self defense, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
- The Final Secret of Life, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Financially Hard Times, no. 1-6, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Fire Down Below! What Some Tampons Do To Our Bodies, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Fit Pitcher, no. 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Five Years, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Flaneur: The Magazine of Art and Other Nonsense, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Flashbulb Memory, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Flowers and Flatulence a.k.a. Sweet Pickles, no. 1-2, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Foot Care, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Frail Roots, no. 2, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Frankenstein Meets Shirley Temple, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Frankenstein Meets Shirley Temple, no. 2, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Fred the Clown, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Fred the Clown, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Free Women of Spain, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Free Your Mind, no. 4, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Freedom of Depression: 9 Ways to Commit Suicide, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Freedom of Depression: No Contact, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
- The Fridge, no. 5, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- From another side: two stories, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- fuckyou pictures from the heart, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Full Sanction in Home Mechanomics, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Full Sanction: The Official Handbook of the Full Sanction Universe, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Full Sanction: Threats, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- functionally ill: adventures with mental health, no. 3-5, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Funeral, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Funeral, no. 48, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Furtile Ground for People who Dig Parenting, no. 1, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Gadgie, no. 21 /Ripping Thrash, no. 23, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Gaza, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
- To Gaza and Back, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Gender, Sexualty, and Women's Studies (at VCU), 2013 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- General Strike - Arm Yoursself with Knowledge, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Genius (Love), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Gentle Graffitti, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Get Back Shirt, no. 5, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Getting a Handle on Yr Women's Health (and trans), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- GFP! (Gender Free Pronoun), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Ghost Story, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Give Me Back, no. 5, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Glass Orchid, no. 2, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Glass Orchid, no. 4, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Glows in the Dark presents The Warren Oates Suite, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Good Morning, "Unknown", no. 3, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
- ground zero, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Gullible, no. 21/Gray Matter, no. 4, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Guillible, no. 24, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Gutwrench, no. 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Gray Matter, no. 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Gray Matter, no. 3, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Green Graffiti, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- The Gringo Manifesto, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Hamaterama, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- harlot, RN, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Heartattack: hardcore for the hardcore, no. 8, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Heartwarming and Pathetic: Collected Journal Entries, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Heaven & Hell, vol. II no. 5, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Here It Is, no. 3, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Hinckley whistlin' dixie, no. 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Hinckley whistlin' dixie, no. 2, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- hoax, no. 1, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- The Hole, no. 1-4, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- How 2 Zine, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- How 2 Zine, no. 2, How 2 Zine Distro, undated, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- A How to Guide on Starting a DIY Events Calendar (in your town), 2009 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- How to Make a Bike innertube Wallet Hurrah!, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
- How to write a Zine or the art of procrastination, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- The Hpv Zine, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- I Heart Condoms: I Heart Sex, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- i Heart Dudes: I Heart Sex, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
- I Heart Fantasies: I Heart Sex, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- I Heart Orgasma! I Heart Sex, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
- I am from the cave, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- I Bleed Scorpions, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- I Dream of "Dreams of Donuts", undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- I Love Bad Movies, no. 2-5, 2010-2012 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- I Heart the World even though it's ugly, no. 3, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- idle tuesday, no. 2, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
- ikea, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Imagine having hope again, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- In rhythm & sorrow, no. 2, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ?Ni una m?s!, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Indy, no. 4, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- imaginary windows, no. 4, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Inside Front, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Insomnia: A Warrior's Guide, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Insurrectionary Mutual Aid, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- interiority, no.10, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Intelligence Failure, no. 1-2, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Intricate Dwellings, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Introvert, no. 4-6, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Ishkabibble, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- it Works Because it is Dirty, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Jetsom, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Journal of Disenchantment, no. 2-3, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Joyful Dissent, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Juniper, The, no. 9, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Keep Loving, Keep Fighting, no. 8, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Keller, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Keloid, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Kickstand, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Kneehigh (roadside stuff), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- La-La Theory, The, no. 6, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Lac du Flambeau Treaty Rights, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Lack of Affection, no. 1 (aka Introvert no. 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Last Prom: eclectic esoterica for a better tomorrow, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Laterborn, no. 1, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Learning to Leave a Paper Trail, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Learnout, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Let's Go to the Park, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Liberate RVA (Folder 1 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Liberate RVA (Folder 2 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
- The Light is Much too Bright, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- The Light is Much too Bright, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- The Light is Much too Bright Vol. 1, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- The Light is Much too Bright, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- The Light is Much too Bright, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- The Light is Much too Bright, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lips(tick) Service, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Lips: Expressions of Female Sexuality (three issues), undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lips: Expressions of Female Sexuality, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Little Blue Book no. 468 and a printed card, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Little Fable, A, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- little ones or birds against squirrels, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- liner notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Lipgloss, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- The London Zine Symposium: tales form the first 5 years, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Long Walk Back to Myself, The, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Lonesome Utah, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Lunatext Experiment in Awareness, no. 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Mag Hags: 200 years of Feminist Zines, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Magic Prize, no. 2, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Magnatozia, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Make Believe, no. 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Manifesto Baby, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Marginal Therapy, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Mark's Little Book about Kinder Eggs, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- The Masochistic Forum, no. 1, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
- The Masochistic Forum, no. 2, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
- The Masochistic Forum, no. 4, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Me, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Meanwhile at SPX 2006, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Meanwhile at SPX 2007, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Meanwhile at SPX 2008, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- M?lange, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Memory/Boundary: Things Collected from Buildings and Streets, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Metamorphosis of Miss Badass Peacock and Kizzy, The, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Method Manson Skynyrd, The, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Minutes from Midnight, no. 3-4, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- minutiae, no. 1, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- minutiae, no. 2, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- minutiae, no. 3, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Missed Connections, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Mistaken Clean Air System, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Mistaken for Straight, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Mole, no. 3, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Monster, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Monster issue 6, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Monster Fetus, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Monster Gripes, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Monsters in Sweaters, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Monstress, no. 6-7, 2004, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Mother, may I take three big steps?, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Mountaintopism, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Mr. Nile: The Illustrated Bastard, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Mrs. Noggle, no. 13, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Mugwhump's Big Night, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Murrow's Hope, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Muse, nos. 1-3, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- My First Angela Y. Davis Zine, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
- My Letter to the World, no. 13, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- My Summer of Potter: A Harry Potter Subculture Zine, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
- My Time Anninilator: A Brief History of 1930s Science Fiction, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Naked: Kill Art, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Naked: The Art of Sticker Warfare, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Naked: Collected Works, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Nakid Funzine, no. 6, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Native Son, no. 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Neat, no. 1, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Meckmonster, no. 6, 8, 2004, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Negative Capability, no. 1, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- New Illustrated Interstrange, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- New to Everything, no. 7, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Ninja Force Sketch Book, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Nihilistic Times, no. 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Not Kathy, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Nothing, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- nothing is cool, no. 5, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
- not sorry no. 3 the unofficial riot grrrl issue, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Now Meet Satan, no. 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
- NSA Famous, no. 1, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
- (Old) Woman Question, The, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ohno (A Collection of e-mails), undated (Box 15, Folder 2)